<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>joey trampush phd</title>
    <link>https://brainworkup.org/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content on joey trampush phd</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; {year} Joey Trampush</copyright>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://brainworkup.org/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An example conference paper</title>
      <link>https://brainworkup.org/publication/conference-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brainworkup.org/publication/conference-paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplementary notes can be added here, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34;&gt;code and math&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An example journal article</title>
      <link>https://brainworkup.org/publication/journal-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brainworkup.org/publication/journal-article/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable
visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management
software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo academia&amp;rsquo;s Markdown
slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplementary notes can be added here, including
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34;&gt;code and math&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day One</title>
      <link>https://brainworkup.org/2022/11/19/day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brainworkup.org/2022/11/19/day-one/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;div id=&#34;TOC&#34;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#motivation&#34; id=&#34;toc-motivation&#34;&gt;Motivation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#why-this-topic&#34; id=&#34;toc-why-this-topic&#34;&gt;Why this topic?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#audience-for-this-book&#34; id=&#34;toc-audience-for-this-book&#34;&gt;Audience for this book&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#this-book-will-then-be-of-interest-to-two-groups&#34; id=&#34;toc-this-book-will-then-be-of-interest-to-two-groups&#34;&gt;This book will then be of interest to two groups:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#but-what-is-production&#34; id=&#34;toc-but-what-is-production&#34;&gt;But what is “production”?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#book-structure&#34; id=&#34;toc-book-structure&#34;&gt;Book structure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;motivation&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This book will not get you started with shiny, nor talk how to work with shiny once it is sent to production.
What we will be discussing in this book is the process of building an application that will later be sent to production.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;why-this-topic&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why this topic?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lots of blog posts and books talk about getting started with shiny (Chang et al. 2020) or about what to do once your application is ready to be sent to production.
Very few (if any) talk about this area in-between: how to confidently work with shiny once you know the basics, and before you send it to production.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what this book is going to talk about: building robust shiny applications that are ready to be sent to production.
We’ll focus on the process, the workflow, and the necessary tools for building production-grade shiny applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;audience-for-this-book&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Audience for this book&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are starting to read this book, we assume you have a working knowledge of how to build a small application using shiny, and want to know how to go one step further.
In other words, you already have some knowledge about how shiny works, are able to build a small working application, and want to know how to build a serious, production-grade application that can be sent to production.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The content of this book oscillates between conceptual discussions (e.g., what is complexity?), exploration of project-management questions (e.g., how do we organize work when building production shiny applications?), and technical topics (e.g., what are shiny modules, or how do I optimize shiny?), with a large portion of the book being dedicated to technical questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;this-book-will-then-be-of-interest-to-two-groups&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;This book will then be of interest to two groups:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Team managers who want to help to organize work, and shiny developers who want to learn about project management.
This group will find relevant content in the first 1/3 of this book (roughly until Chapter 5).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Developers who want to cover medium to advanced shiny topics that will be relevant to production.
This group will be more interested in the rest of the book, which roughly spans from Chapter 6 to the end.
Note that the technical elements covered in this book range from intermediate to advanced topics, and we hope that you will find relevant topics for your current goals, whatever your level is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In practice, we’ve come to realize that a lot of shiny projects are built by small teams with a large number of these “teams” being composed of only one developer.
In this context, we have realized that project management and development are often assigned to the very same person,1 making these two skills deeply integrated when carrying production projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s why this book tries to reconcile both these worlds, as building production-grade software needs a reliable and operational code-base which is made possible by having solid technical skills, but also reliable and operational team work and project management.
What is “production”?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All throughout this book, we will be using the term “production” to refer to the way we build and deploy our application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;but-what-is-production&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;But what is “production”?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There have been a lot of definitions of what production is, and even today if you ask around you will get a wide range of different answers.
We like to think that a piece of software is in production when it combines the three following properties, not only for the users, but also the engineers working on it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is used, even if only by one person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is relied upon by its user(s).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has real life impact if something goes wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These three properties impact two specific groups: users and the developers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the users rely on the app to work so that they can do their job, and expect it to deliver meaningful results that they can count on.
From the engineering point of view, a production-grade software can be relied upon in the sense that developers count on it to run as expected, and they need to rely on the software to be resilient to change, i.e to be modular, documented, and strongly tested so that changes can be integrated with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A production software also has real-life impact if something goes wrong: users will make wrong decisions, they might be unable to do their day-to-day work, and there are all the things that can happen when the software you use on a daily basis fails to run.
From the engineering point of view, a production-grade software has real impact when something goes wrong: someone has to fix the bug, the company selling the software might lose money, data can be lost, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Given these two properties, you can understand why being in production doesn’t necessarily mean being served to gazillions of users,2 and serving trillions of gigabytes of data: even software that is used by one person who relies on this application to do their job is a production software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what this book is about: building shiny applications that can be used, on which you and your users can rely, and including all the tools that will help you prevent things from going wrong, and when they eventually do, making sure you are equipped to quickly fix the bugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;book-structure&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Book structure&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part 1, “Building Successful shiny Apps” gives a general context for what we mean by “production-grade” and “successful” shiny applications, and what challenges arise when you are dealing with a large-scale application designed for production.
In this part, we will define what we mean by “Successful”, stress the importance of project management, develop how to structure your project for production, and introduce the golem (Fay et al. 2021) package.
We will finally, briefly introduce to our development workflow: a workflow that will be explored in Parts 2 to 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part 2 through 6 explore the workflow for building successful applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part 2: Design (Step 1) underlines the centrality of the user experience when engineering an application, and emphasizes the importance of designing before coding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part 3: Prototype (Step 2) stresses the importance of prototyping, explores the setting of a golem-based application, and presents shinipsum, fakir, and the “Rmd First” development methodology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part 4: Build (Step 3) explores the building step of the application, i.e the core engineering of the application once the prototyping phase is finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part 5: Strengthen (Step 4) explores in-depth testing, continuous integration, and version control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part 6: Deploy (Step 5) develops the various possibilities for preparing your application to be deployed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part 7, “Optimizing” tackles the question of optimization, first by introducing the general concepts about optimization, then by presenting some common caveats of shiny apps, and then showing how to optimize R code, and how to use JavaScript to lighten R work.
This part ends with a gentle introduction to CSS (Cascading Style Sheets).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highcharter Drilldown on Neuropsychological Domains</title>
      <link>https://brainworkup.org/2022/04/05/highcharter-drilldown-neurocognitive-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brainworkup.org/2022/04/05/highcharter-drilldown-neurocognitive-domains/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2022/04/05/highcharter-drilldown-neurocognitive-domains/index_files/htmlwidgets/htmlwidgets.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2022/04/05/highcharter-drilldown-neurocognitive-domains/index_files/pymjs/pym.v1.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2022/04/05/highcharter-drilldown-neurocognitive-domains/index_files/widgetframe-binding/widgetframe.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;TOC&#34;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#neuropsychological-testing-results&#34; id=&#34;toc-neuropsychological-testing-results&#34;&gt;Neuropsychological Testing Results&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;neuropsychological-testing-results&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Neuropsychological Testing Results&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
aside {
  margin-left: 100%;
  position: absolute;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
img {
  width: 200vw;
  margin-left: calc(50% - 50vw);
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
rect[Attributes Style] {
    fill: transparent;
    x: 0;
    y: 0;
    width: 1200;
    height: 800;
    rx: 0;
    ry: 0;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
.drilld {
  width: 300vw;
  margin-left: calc(50% - 50vw);
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;figure&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:block;&#34; id=&#34;fig:drilldown-plot&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;htmlwidget-1&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;height:768px;&#34; class=&#34;widgetframe html-widget&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/json&#34; data-for=&#34;htmlwidget-1&#34;&gt;{&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;url&#34;:&#34;figs//widgets/widget_drilldown-plot.html&#34;,&#34;options&#34;:{&#34;xdomain&#34;:&#34;*&#34;,&#34;allowfullscreen&#34;:false,&#34;lazyload&#34;:false}},&#34;evals&#34;:[],&#34;jsHooks&#34;:[]}&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;p class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;
Figure 1: HighchartR Drilldown
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiny Document</title>
      <link>https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/27/shiny-document/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/27/shiny-document/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;link href=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/27/shiny-document/index_files/selectize/css/selectize.bootstrap3.css&#34; rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; /&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/27/shiny-document/index_files/selectize/js/selectize.min.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/27/shiny-document/index_files/selectize/accessibility/js/selectize-plugin-a11y.min.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/27/shiny-document/index_files/ionrangeslider-javascript/js/ion.rangeSlider.min.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/27/shiny-document/index_files/strftime/strftime-min.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link href=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/27/shiny-document/index_files/ionrangeslider-css/css/ion.rangeSlider.css&#34; rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; /&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;TOC&#34;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#section-inputs-and-outputs&#34; id=&#34;section-toc-inputs-and-outputs&#34;&gt;Inputs and Outputs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#section-embedded-application&#34; id=&#34;section-toc-embedded-application&#34;&gt;Embedded Application&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This R Markdown document is made interactive using Shiny.
Unlike the more traditional workflow of creating static reports, you can now create documents that allow your readers to change the assumptions underlying your analysis and see the results immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more, see &lt;a href=&#34;http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com/authoring_shiny.html&#34;&gt;Interactive Documents&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;section-inputs-and-outputs&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Inputs and Outputs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can embed Shiny inputs and outputs in your document.
Outputs are automatically updated whenever inputs change.
This demonstrates how a standard R plot can be made interactive by wrapping it in the Shiny &lt;code&gt;renderPlot&lt;/code&gt; function.
The &lt;code&gt;selectInput&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;sliderInput&lt;/code&gt; functions create the input widgets used to drive the plot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;shiny-input-panel&#34;&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;shiny-flow-layout&#34;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;form-group shiny-input-container&#34;&gt;
&lt;label class=&#34;control-label&#34; id=&#34;n_breaks-label&#34; for=&#34;n_breaks&#34;&gt;Number of bins:&lt;/label&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;select id=&#34;n_breaks&#34;&gt;&lt;option value=&#34;10&#34;&gt;10&lt;/option&gt;
&lt;option value=&#34;20&#34; selected&gt;20&lt;/option&gt;
&lt;option value=&#34;35&#34;&gt;35&lt;/option&gt;
&lt;option value=&#34;50&#34;&gt;50&lt;/option&gt;&lt;/select&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/json&#34; data-for=&#34;n_breaks&#34; data-nonempty=&#34;&#34;&gt;{&#34;plugins&#34;:[&#34;selectize-plugin-a11y&#34;]}&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;form-group shiny-input-container&#34;&gt;
&lt;label class=&#34;control-label&#34; id=&#34;bw_adjust-label&#34; for=&#34;bw_adjust&#34;&gt;Bandwidth adjustment:&lt;/label&gt;
&lt;input class=&#34;js-range-slider&#34; id=&#34;bw_adjust&#34; data-skin=&#34;shiny&#34; data-min=&#34;0.2&#34; data-max=&#34;2&#34; data-from=&#34;1&#34; data-step=&#34;0.2&#34; data-grid=&#34;true&#34; data-grid-num=&#34;9&#34; data-grid-snap=&#34;false&#34; data-prettify-separator=&#34;,&#34; data-prettify-enabled=&#34;true&#34; data-keyboard=&#34;true&#34; data-data-type=&#34;number&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;shiny-plot-output html-fill-item&#34; id=&#34;outa20730549e86ce03&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;height:400px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;section-embedded-application&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Embedded Application&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s also possible to embed an entire Shiny application within an R Markdown document using the &lt;code&gt;shinyAppDir&lt;/code&gt; function.
This example embeds a Shiny application located in another directory:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe data-deferred-src=&#34;appba07d34b5cd679e86ff2e0476fa46fdb/?w=&amp;amp;__subapp__=1&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;550&#34; class=&#34;shiny-frame shiny-frame-deferred&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note the use of the &lt;code&gt;height&lt;/code&gt; parameter to determine how much vertical space the embedded application should occupy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also use the &lt;code&gt;shinyApp&lt;/code&gt; function to define an application inline rather then in an external directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In all of R code chunks above the &lt;code&gt;echo = FALSE&lt;/code&gt; attribute is used.
This is to prevent the R code within the chunk from rendering in the document alongside the Shiny components.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drilldown on Neuropsych Data with R</title>
      <link>https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/18/npsych-drilldown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/18/npsych-drilldown/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/18/npsych-drilldown/index_files/htmlwidgets/htmlwidgets.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/18/npsych-drilldown/index_files/pymjs/pym.v1.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://brainworkup.org/2021/06/18/npsych-drilldown/index_files/widgetframe-binding/widgetframe.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;TOC&#34;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#highcharter-drilldown-setup&#34; id=&#34;toc-highcharter-drilldown-setup&#34;&gt;Highcharter Drilldown Setup&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#r-markdown-chunk-options&#34; id=&#34;toc-r-markdown-chunk-options&#34;&gt;R Markdown chunk options&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#load-libraries&#34; id=&#34;toc-load-libraries&#34;&gt;Load libraries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#import-data&#34; id=&#34;toc-import-data&#34;&gt;Import data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#drilldown-using-percentiles&#34; id=&#34;toc-drilldown-using-percentiles&#34;&gt;Drilldown using percentiles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#drilldown-using-zscores&#34; id=&#34;toc-drilldown-using-zscores&#34;&gt;Drilldown using zScores&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;highcharter-drilldown-setup&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Highcharter Drilldown Setup&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;r-markdown-chunk-options&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;R Markdown chunk options&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;load-libraries&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Load libraries&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
aside {
  margin-left: 100%;
  position: absolute;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
img {
  width: 100vw;
  margin-left: calc(50% - 50vw);
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
rect[Attributes Style] {
    fill: transparent;
    x: 0;
    y: 0;
    width: 800;
    height: 500;
    rx: 0;
    ry: 0;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;import-data&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Import data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;drilldown-using-percentiles&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Drilldown using percentiles&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;style type=&#34;text/css&#34;&gt;
.drilld {
  width: 100vw;
  margin-left: calc(50% - 50vw);
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;figure&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:block;&#34; id=&#34;fig:drillp&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;htmlwidget-1&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;height:480px;&#34; class=&#34;widgetframe html-widget&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/json&#34; data-for=&#34;htmlwidget-1&#34;&gt;{&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;url&#34;:&#34;index_files/figure-html//widgets/widget_drillp.html&#34;,&#34;options&#34;:{&#34;xdomain&#34;:&#34;*&#34;,&#34;allowfullscreen&#34;:false,&#34;lazyload&#34;:false}},&#34;evals&#34;:[],&#34;jsHooks&#34;:[]}&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;p class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;
Figure 1: Drilldown Neuropsych Pct
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;drilldown-using-zscores&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Drilldown using zScores&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;figure&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:block;&#34; id=&#34;fig:drillz&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;htmlwidget-2&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;height:480px;&#34; class=&#34;widgetframe html-widget&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/json&#34; data-for=&#34;htmlwidget-2&#34;&gt;{&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;url&#34;:&#34;index_files/figure-html//widgets/widget_drillz.html&#34;,&#34;options&#34;:{&#34;xdomain&#34;:&#34;*&#34;,&#34;allowfullscreen&#34;:false,&#34;lazyload&#34;:false}},&#34;evals&#34;:[],&#34;jsHooks&#34;:[]}&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;p class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;
Figure 2: Drilldown Neuropsych zScores
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An example preprint / working paper</title>
      <link>https://brainworkup.org/publication/preprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brainworkup.org/publication/preprint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo academia&amp;rsquo;s Markdown slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplementary notes can be added here, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34;&gt;code and math&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
